<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>outcomes.fyi</title>
    <link href="http://www.outcomes.fyi/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="http://www.outcomes.fyi" />
    <updated>2021-06-17T08:11:40-07:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Arnaud</name>
    </author>
    <id>http://www.outcomes.fyi</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Testimonials</title>
        <author>
            <name>Arnaud</name>
        </author>
        <link href="http://www.outcomes.fyi/testimonials.html"/>
        <id>http://www.outcomes.fyi/testimonials.html</id>

        <updated>2021-06-17T08:11:40-07:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <blockquote>
<p>I'm Mark and I am an administrator for a private middle school. Thanks to Outcomes, I was able to find out who among our teachers provided our students with the greatest chances of success later in life and rewarded them accordingly.</p>
<p>Before Outcomes, I really had no idea what our students become after they graduate from our school.</p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<p>My name is Jill and I am a practicing physician in a clinic. With the help of Outcomes, I was able to better measure how my patients fared in the long run when dealing with chronic conditions such as diabetes or hypertension. It helped me dial in the best practices for my patients.</p>
<p>Before, I would lost track of 80%+ of my patients over time and was left wondering which treatments provided the most beneficial long term outcomes. Outcomes helps me do this effortlessly.</p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<p>My name is Henry and I manage a charitable fund for wealthy individuals. We deploy millions of dollars every year in the hope of improving the lives of others through our social and education programs. The most frequent question I receive from our many donators is how efficient our programs have been.</p>
<p>Are we allocating our limited ressources towards the best-in-class associations, non-profits and social entrepeneurs?</p>
<p>Are we truly changing the lives of the people we care for in a meaningful and lasting way?</p>
<p>Outcomes have answered all these questions and more for us. We have been able to double down on our best programs and reallocate millions of dollars towards our most impactful social enterprises.</p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<p>I am Monica and I work for the State government. Three years ago, we rolled out a tax credit to promote the adoption of electric vehicles. We must now consider whether to extend this program in its current form and Outcomes have been instrumental in helping us understand which taxpayers were able to take advantage of the credit and how many tons of CO2 and local air pollution were prevented thanks to this program. </p>
</blockquote>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Learn more</title>
        <author>
            <name>Arnaud</name>
        </author>
        <link href="http://www.outcomes.fyi/come-back-soon.html"/>
        <id>http://www.outcomes.fyi/come-back-soon.html</id>

        <updated>2021-06-16T22:38:27-07:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p class="align-center"><a href="mailto:ask@outcomes.fyi">ask@outcomes.fyi</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
